Hi.
And today I have with me Brad Brewer.
Owner of the Brad Brewer Golf Academy at the beautiful Rose Shingle Creek in Orlando, Florida.
We're talking about self hypnosis.
And in this segment we're going to talk about why it's import to properly breathe deeply.
And Brad is going to show us how to breathe deeply.
Right.
Thank you.
So the most important thing.
And Brad knows this because he's done a lot of self hypnosis to help him improve his golf game.
Even though he's a top 100 instructor already.
But even they can improve.
And with deep breathing you will learn how important it is to begin this relaxation step.
So in order to deep breathe we always begin at the very bottom of our stomach.
So Brad if you could put your hands on the bottom of your stomach so that we can see your hands expanding.
And you always want to start at the very bottom of your stomach.
In fact everyone push your stomach out.
We want you to imagine that your stomach's like a balloon and we have to push the balloon out so that we can breathe in.
And he's going to breathe all the way up.
And he's going to breathe.
In fact he could, you can keep your eyes open or closed, whatever you prefer Brad.
But he's going to breathe all the way up in fact as if the breath is touching the top of his head.
Now we know that your lungs stop here but he's going to breathe as if it's coming to this place.
So breath all the way up.
Breathe, breathe, breathe, breathe in through your nose and you always exhale through your nose.
Exhale through your nose.
And you can see how his shoulders and his chest and his stomach deflate.
And then he pushes his stomach out.
He breathes in as deep as he can all the way up with his nose.
That's great.
And then he breathes out.
All the way down.
See how his shoulders come down, his chest comes down, and his stomach comes down.
That is the proper way to breathe.
Always breathe from the very bottom of your stomach.
Pull the breath up to the highest part that you can get it and then relax it down as if a balloon is deflating.
Breathe in through the nose and out through the nose.
And that's the proper way to breathe deeply.